So friends, if you have taken a home loan, the borrower dies after taking the home loan, then
what will happen in that situation, whether the bank will take possession of the property or some
discount can be given that Kandahar has died. If it is, then by giving this much discount, should we make people dross
or will this Mike be restricted, is this type of discount given to the borrower even if
it is not given, friends, all the questions will be answered through this video
I am going to share, I hope that you will like the information, if you like it, please do
not forget to like share this video and subscribe to the YouTube channel. Friends, whenever you take a home loan,
you are given an insurance along with the home loan. Friends go to secure your home loan, there
is a production plan, its amount is a side effect in your loan, and for the number of years that loan is
taken, the production planning goes on, friends, it is good to tell you that
when If you take production alarm then suppose you took home loan for 10 years and production
clamp 20 man runs before 10 years if suppose you
do this bakery for 2 years and after 2 years on EMI it becomes yours no it If 1000 dies, then
what is inside that condition, whatever you guys have secured from the production plane, then the
company that is on the insurance side, that company, Sarah's whole homework, their money, the home loan company. Provides to you
and makes you debt free, the property papers that you have come to you
friends, even if you have taken a home loan for two years from where you have taken
all the money You also get all the money back with interest Friends, I would like to tell you
that home loan production love has the advantage that life is uncertain, so whenever you borrow money, now I
have an account so that after the death of the borrower, no one should face any problem. Or the property does not go into the possession of the bank,
so you must take the home loan in the play, friends, this has been its advantage, now we
know that
what will happen in the situation of the person who did not take the production alarm of the home loan. Either the bank will take possession
of his property or he is given a discount or
according to the report a decision is taken from there. Means if home loan is insured
then no one talks about it even after death everything gets settled friends but suppose Kareena
died after taking home loan and those people did not take production plant i.e. bank
Told them to take the problem but reduced their faith in the solution, refused, so
focused on the condition that what will happen after the death of the friends, the bank
can take possession of the properties but the owner of the property It means that the properties which
have been passed by the owner and biological, after that those who are living in that house can reduce, this thing can go in the post, so
friends, what happens simply for that situation, whatever happens to that property. That person is the legal heir,
that person will have to pay all the money of the home loan, whether through Mi or he
can loot, because friends, the owner of the home loan died, but that person After
whatever the legal heir of the property has to be loaned to that person, the bank has the right that it
can draw it inside the court and inside the closet, the same thing will come out to the person who
is the legal heir. Money has to be packed, now if this also goes away, then normally it will remain the same as before,
but even if the final montage is done, it is a different topic, friends, the bank does this because the
owner of that property will be the heir because of what he had If there is a death, then the job owner
can give him a dominant leg to the bank or send a notice to him and say that for the amount, friends
do opium devices, whether we should take this reproduction or not, MS would like to tell you, friends,
to take a hundred percent. Friends, we assume that the borrower died after taking the home loan and
had not taken any secure plan i.e. did not take insurance .
Friends of your home loan, what should be done under these two circumstances,
friends, whatever the legal heirs on top of the property or those who are in the house,
those people should give a request to the bank that they should go inside the bank to pay off your home loan.
Respect what is there, give respect to what is there again, so that what is Mi becomes less
and if you do not face any problem in presenting it to people, then what happens by researching that this mic
becomes less and If the burden of this is reduced, then friends, it is a mutual understanding that you
and the bank will have tight containers inside, then you can go and request them that if you did
not even take the question time and your career died, then Friends, this one Abe Chanakya craftsman will come, if he is
going out and requesting that he respect our home loan, so
that this money becomes smaller and it will not be easy for you to pay, friends, this is Then all
the information related to this, if you want any information, then you
can comment me in the comment box, I will try my best to give you the best answer, friends, how is this video, if you like my video,
like share and YouTube Don't forget to subscribe the channel thanks guys